Hey there.
Uh quick update.
Uh we've refactored the explore view. So
now it's more Jupiter-like notebook view
and you can use the whole explore view
using just the keyboard. If you don't
want to, you don't need to be forced to
it. You can also it has a pretty good
usability by just clicking around and
writing the queries you need.
Okay? But if you want if you are kind of
a power dev user that's like in love
with Jupiter and all that stuff, you can
press
um
interrogation mark and find uh all the
all the shortcuts that you need.
Uh also we have introduced an AI
assistant.
So it can help you write the queries
that you need. For example, let me see,
get me all the metric names for my
project.
Okay?
And then it writes the query and then
you can find everything that you need.
Okay?
We also have uh now a bit more
information on on the left on the
records. You have all the all the
[snorts] the possible columns you have
access, metrics, and also the functions
that you can use on your
um
uh on your explore view. Okay?
Thank you.
>> [music]